So you'll leave?
Yes.
I'm almost completely healed.
Laozi's medicine helped.
I've got mixed feelings.
I'm glad you're healed,
but we'll miss you.
I'll visit you guys often.
You haven't told Xiaobai yet, have you?
No.
How much time do you need?
By tomorrow I'll be fine.
Can you take a human form?
Yes.
Wow, can you show it to me?
It's awkward to transform in front of you.
I understand.
So you will leave tomorrow?
Won't you rest some more?
I'd rather finish the quest.
I'll visit you after that.
Okay.
Go, say goodbye to Xiaobai.
Sure.
Before I forget.
Can you lend me some clothes?
I reverted to my base state.
My clothes didn't survive.
Sure, I can.
Early today morning, an aircraft of
MT Airlines crashed in Longyou City.
The passengers were discovered on roofs of houses near the site.
Lawful Ones
and Lawless Ones
The cause of the baffling phenomenon is under investigation.
We interviewed a fortunate survivor.
I don't care what it was.
From this day on,
I believe in God's existence.
I thank him for saving me.
I will cherish my life even more.
It must have been a spirit.
Incidents involving spirits are
on the news 10-20 times a year.
So many?
So few, actually.
Many spirits live secluded.
Those who live among humans, must hide their identities.
Aside from incidents like this,
most of them never get exposed.
The club hall prohibits flying over the city.
He'll be punished.
How do you know their rules so well?
I used to live there.
I see.
So every spirit lives in hiding?
Not at all.
A lot of them make good use of their abilities in the human world.
Some are even rich and famous.
How do you know that?
Spirit boards, tabloid section.
Oh...
What?
I go sunbathing.
I'll leave only tomorrow.
I can tell her then.
I'll leave soon.
Always listen to Xiaobai.
If you don't behave, they won't keep you.
Good morning, boss!
Good morning.
I think I've heard the ex-boss.
Is he on a trip?
He's having fun.
I check it out.
Boss!!
Silence.
Boss!
A lot of our comrades have disappeared.
What if it's...?
Leave it to me.
Daddy!
Hello, dear! Had breakfast yet?
Who'll be at the door first?
Me, me, me!
Boss!
They're empty!
How did they escape?
Stop!
A cat spirit?
Kid!
What do you want?
Let him go.
Why exactly?
All right.
I can do that much for you.
It's rare I meet someone of my kind.
But tell me, little fellow,
why do you want to save a human like this?
Spirits, humans, animals.
Whose side are you on?
None of your business.
Stop kidnapping humans!
Do you know the local club hall?
Yes.
I've got special permission from them.
In other words, I'm a lawful hunter.
What?
But I have no intention to become your enemy about such a thing.
I'll try to avoid you.
Let's not meet again, kitten!
Daddy!
Daddy, are you all right? Daddy!
Xiaohei.
What are you doing up there?
Sunbathing?
Let's hang the clothes.
Directed by:
Mutou
Key animation:
Gen
Kali
Dongdong
Xiao Rong
Koukou
Lizi
Storyboard:
Fanzi
Animation:
Rou Shan
Yezi
Jiu Jiu
Luo Yi
OZ
Shiyue
Design:
Fenmo
Dandan
Youzi
Mountain Bodhisattva
(Shan Sa)
Backgrounds:
Mang Yan
Qi Feng
Mao Zha
Modeling:
Da Shuang
Lulu
Kui Zhi
Xiao Yu
Sun Gua
Xiao Xuan
Big What (Da Ma)
Little Bird (Xiaoniao)
Hao Ke
Kangzi
Bro Jie (Jie Ge)
Ahe
Old Jiang (Lao Jiang)
Service staff:
Hu Niu
Huanhuan
Tu Yi
Kucha
Character design:
Biti
Maomao
Atom (Yuanzi)
Coffin (Guancai)
Xiaobai, Xiaohei, Gen,
Reporter, Little Girl, Doggie:
Shan Xin
Niepa, Man:
Everyone else:
Tong Yin
Xiaolang
New Moon Ice (Xinyue Bingbing)
Sound engineer:
Sugar Little Sugar
(Tang Xiaotang)
Piyu:
Tao Bao
Heishu:
Ai Suo
Sound:
Sun Yujing
Xu Wei
Bohe
Wang Miao
Howdy, Xiaohei!
Enjoying sunshine?
I've got some good stuff.
Have you ever tasted the flavor of life?
Take a sip.
What's This Taste?
Xiaohei?
What do you think, what's wrong with Xiaohei?
Seemingly there's nothing wrong.
He's got a fever.
It can't be.
Spirits don't catch human illnesses.
Also, a cat's body is warmer than a human's.
I see...
Hello? Shan Xin?
No, don't come over!
Just one question.
Maybe he yearns for a girl.
What??
Do you want me to lend you Huang?
Oh, shut up...
You should take him to a vet.
Okay, thanks.
Can we take him to a vet?
Absolutely not.
Also, it wouldn't help.
I thought so.
Xiaohei!
It's like he's drunk...
Gen, come quick!
They're just Heishus.
What on earth is this?
Now he's sleeping sound.
Maybe he's just tired?
What do we do now?
Have a cup!
Don't worry, he'll be all right.
↓
Awfully
precious
No!!
This is not good...
Stay here for a while.
Xiaohei, you're up?
What's that smell?
Let them go.
I will when you get better.
Now have some rest.
You wanna fight?
Stop it!
He really got stronger...
What am I doing here?
What happened?
Feeling better?
I release the Heishus then.
Just now...
Again?!
Stop it!
Yoohoo, I'm home!
What happened here?!
Grandpa...
Directed by:
Mutou
Storyboard:
Kali
Scenario:
Mutou
Not Yet Blue (Wei Lan)
Key animation:
Gen
Kali
Dongdong
Xiao Rong
Koukou
Lizi
Dai Wei
Modeling:
Da Shuang
Lulu
Kui Zhi
Xiao Yu
Sun Gua
Xiao Xuan
Backgrounds:
Mang Yan
Qi Feng
Mao Zha
Animation:
Rou Shan
Yezi
Jiu Jiu
Luo Yi
OZ
Shiyue
Da Bai
Bro Heng (Heng Ge)
Design:
Fenmo
Dandan
Youzi
Shan Sa
Service staff:
Hu Niu
Huanhuan
Tu Yi
Kucha
Da Ma
Xiaoniao
Hao Ke
Kangzi
Jie Ge
Ahe
Lao Jiang
Maomao
Yuanzi
Ranpo (Luan Bu)
Zero Two (Ling Er)
Evening (Axi)
Xiaobai, Xiaohei, Gen,
Shan Xin, Xiaohuang:
Shan Xin
Grandpa:
Huang Zhenji
Sound engineer:
Tang Xiaotang
Piyu:
Tao Bao
Heishu:
Ai Suo
Sound:
Sun Yujing
Xu Wei
Bohe
Wang Miao
It won't
happen again
Xiaohei?
Xiaobai.
I must leave now.
You really have to leave now?
Yeah...
Did I scare you?
I knew it was you the moment I saw you.
So you can transform into human form!
I've never thought you can.
I'm not so good at it yet.
How come your hair is white?
Oh, you mean this?
It used to be black.
So you really are older than Grandpa?
No, no. I'm 10 years old too.
When's your birthday?
Around November 1st.
Younger than me. You could be my little brother.
"Around"?
I don't know when I was born.
My master picked a day for me.
You must return to him now?
No, first I have to finish a quest.
So you will come back sometime?
Of course. I'll introduce you to Master later.
He's the best person in the whole world!
Be back as soon as you can!
Xiaohei!
Xiaohei?
Xiaohei has left.
You knew all along that he was going to leave?
Yes.
He wanted to stay here only to heal.
I miss Dad and Mom a little...
They'd be happy to hear this.
Hi, Xiaobai!!
Long time no see
We are fine
We're on
a rollercoaster
Please don't
call now
Whatcha saying??
I can't hear you!!
Parting and Reunion
Grandpa, I'm going swimming!
Okay.
Piyu, come!
I'll be back as soon as I can!!
What?
Manager!
Oh, Mr. Xiaohei.
Can I use the hall's teleport system?
Sure. Where do you need to go?
To Longyou.
Setting out for your next quest?
You know about it?
Yes. But you don't have to go to Longyou.
Why?
Hey, kitten!
How you're doing?
How do you know it's me?
You've never seen my human form.
I've been watching you for a while.
And of course that little girl.
What did you say?
Don't take it the wrong way!
She can't be in the scope of my hunting permit.
I just came to travel.
I'll go up by myself, Manager.
Okay.
You permit humans getting hunted?
He's special.
His name is Niepa.
He's a man-eater.
Man-eater?
Yes.
Even we can't prohibit their kind from hunting.
We can only restrict their permits to "evil people".
Those who they hunt down must be brought here so we can examine them.
Can't they just eat other food?
No. They're like blood eaters.
They too can get nutrition only from a specific food.
All we can do is to inform them about people on death row and vicious criminals.
And conversely:
if they are hunted down by humans,
we don't intervene either.
Can you... really do this?
What else could we do?
We can't deprive them of their right to live.
Ultimately,
they are victims as well.
Not only humans,
but most spirits also loathe them.
But they simply have no choice.
So you guys just let them hunt humans?
Otherwise how?
Do we provide their food?
Or raise it, the same way humans do?
A few days ago, I met Wuxian in Longyou.
He's in Longyou?
No, he already left.
He asked me to give you your next quest.
Thank you.
Manager.
Please read it for me.
Don't forget! Servers start tomorrow at 10.
We can't be late!
I know, you already told me a thousand times.
It's gonna revolutionize gaming.
I guarantee you'll be hooked on it once you played!
Okay, okay, I'll be there on time.
Don't you forget it!
I won't.
Bye!
Bye, bye!
She just can't stop talking when it comes to games.
Sometimes I don't see Shan Xin for days.
How come I don't miss her?
Because you know where to find her.
You're right.
What do you think, when will Xiaohei return?
He only left a day ago.
One day...
What if he's back right away?
I'm back.
Xiaohei!!
What goodbye lasts less than one episode?
Now you're talking like Grandpa.
Have you finished your quest?
Not yet.
I'm here because of it.
Directed by:
Mutou
Key animation:
Gen
Kali
Koukou
Animation:
Lil Nian (Xiao Nian)
Luo Yi
Yezi
Shiyue
Modeling:
Da Shuang
Backgrounds:
Mang Yan
Design:
Fenmo
Youzi
Shan Sa
Xiao Yu
Axi
Character design:
Biti
Service staff:
Hu Niu
Huanhuan
Linlin
Sound:
Sun Yujing
Xu Wei
Bohe
Wang Miao
Xiaobai, Xiaohei,
Gen, Shan Xin:
Shan Xin
Kali:
Xiahou Luofeng
Niepa:
slayerboom
Mom:
Jin Qi
Grandpa:
Huang Zhenji
Project planning:
Zhaozhao
Sound engineer:
Jia Shuaiqiang
Bystanders:
Lao Jiang
Jie Ge
Lizi
Xiao Rong
Dai Wei
Ahe
Ambition (Da Zhi)
Luan Bu
Xiao Huang
Maomao
Lil Cunning (Xiao Rui)
Hao Ke
Ling Er
Mao Zha
Cool Refreshment (Liang Shuang)
Qian Feng
Distance (Yaoyao)
Silence (Jingjing)
Li Heng
Guagua
Sulfuric Acid (Liusuan)
Rou Shan
OZ
Stool (Bandeng)
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
Our destination may be whimsical
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
kore kara deau kimi e to
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Mochiyotta hako aketara
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Are so precious and so fleeting
Omoi wa kitto kienai
Those feelings will never fade away
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete kitto boku wo yonderu
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Kitto boku wo yonderu
And surely, they’re calling out to me